LIBIS PERDIGON

Ridgefield Park, NJ 07660 | 718-669-9604 | Iperdigon@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Residential Interior Design expertise with 10 years of creating and executing design projects. Collaborates with creative and technical teams to produce plans and projects to suit client needs comprehensively. Empowers team members to explore innovative designs to push boundaries while satisfying project requirements.

Architect with demonstrated command of design and marketing. Expert designer with a developed aptitude for Customer Service and sales. Multilingual and fluent in English and Spanish, offering solid comprehension of cultural diversity.

Flexible hard worker ready to learn and contribute to team success. Focused on turning abstract ideas into concrete products which serve clients, employees, and consumers. Assessed client needs while building original and valuable products within the established project budget.

SKILLS

- Critical thinking
- Decision-making
- Friendly, positive attitude
- Problem resolution
- Leadership
- Project planning
- Software skills: AUTOCAD, REVIT ARCHITECTURE, SKETCHUP PRO, ARCHICAD, PHOTOSHOP
- Team building

- Active listening
- Reliable and trustworthy
- Work ethic
- Customer service
- Relationship building
- Multitasking
- Analytical

EXPERIENCE

09/2022 to Current

Interior Architectural Inspector

WSP USA Inspection Services – New York, NY

- Conducted inspections of School Building System Components, equipment, and grounds for deficiencies and evaluated for potential health, safety, and code violations, using proprietary mobile applications.
- Daily inspection of Buildings of more than 150,000 SF.
- Generating daily and detailed reports outlining performance, quality, and defect rates of School Building Conditions.
- Obtaining building data pertaining to complete improvements and upgrades from school staff (Custodial engineers and principals).
- Capturing and reporting correct deficiency quantities.
- Issuing Priority Condition Reports when life safety/hazardous condition exist.

04/2019 to 04/2020 RESIDENTIAL INTERIOR DESIGNER

CAS STUDIO - NEW YORK STATE

- Managed the design team, clients, contractors, and subcontractors.
- Inspected existing spaces, measured dimensions on site, documented, designed features, take photos to reference to purchase fixtures, and assist with style implementation for design projects.

05/2014 to 09/2017 PROJECT MANAGER

ACERO ELEMENTOS C.A. – CARACAS - VENEZUELA, MIRANDA

- Assigned tasks to associates to fit skill levels and maximize team performance.
- Recruited and hired qualified candidates to fill open positions.
- Greeted and encouraged feedback from customers to implement in-store operational changes.
- Conducted inventory counts by assessing the current state of inventory integrity against target accuracy levels and tracking variances.
- Facilitated exceptional sales and performance results by focusing on continuous improvement approaches and capitalizing on emerging market opportunities.
- Evaluated operational trends and proactively adjusted strategies to maintain alignment between performance and objectives.
- Aided in negotiation with vendors and suppliers to reduce overall costs.
- Assisted with training and onboarding of sales associates' in-store operations.
- Completed daily sales reports and analyzed metrics to identify trends.
- Built relationships with internal team members and external partners to enhance the effectiveness of the team's work and boost.

01/2012 to 05/2014 Store Manager

QUALITY METAL C.A. – CARACAS VENEZUELA, MIRANDA

- Delivered excellent customer service and adhered to standard practices to maximize sales and minimize shrinkage.
- Processed daily paperwork, balanced register drawers, produced staffing schedules, and prepared deposits.
- Balanced sales, reconciled cash, and made bank deposits to facilitate opening and closing duties.
- Resolved customer problems by investigating issues, answering questions, and building rapport.
- Strengthened workflow productivity by hiring, managing, and developing top talent.
- Exceeded team goals and resolved issues by sharing and implementing customer service initiatives.
- Improved store status by implementing process improvements and identifying performance gaps for corrective action.
- Oversaw store operations while generating \$ 30.000 in monthly sales.

- Monitored supplier operations to verify quality, delivery schedule, and conformance to contract specifications.
- Boosted sales by 30% by cultivating customer rapport and delivering superior customer service.
- Achieved sales quota of \$20.000 by incorporating anew cap inside the brand.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

11/2021 Digital Marketing

Hudson County Community College – Jersey City, NJ

Bachelor of Architecture

UCV – CARACAS VENEZUELA

Marketing Research

UCV – CARACAS VENEZUELA

Photography

Motivarte – BUENOS AIRES ARGENTINA

Negotiation

Argentine Chamber of Commerce – BUENOS AIRES ARGENTINA

Support And Management of Difficult Customer

Argentine Chamber of Commerce – Buenos Aires Argentina